"use strict"


// **************SEVEN DWARFS TRIVIA  Q/A BEGINNER **************************
//     Be sure to enter correctAnswer based on index # in the array
var questions = [{
    question: "What speed does this ride reach up to?",
    choices: [" Infinity and beyond", " 30 mph", " Dash Incredible speeds", " It is stationary"],
    correctAnswer: 1
}, {
    question: "The queen wanted the huntsman to bring Snow White's heart back in what?",
    choices: [" a sack", " a dingle-hopper", " a jeweled box", " a carriage"],
    correctAnswer: 2
}, {
    question: "What was name was almost used for one of the dwarfs?",
    choices: [" Jumpy", " Buzz", " Moana", " Smee"],
    correctAnswer: 0
}, {
    question: "The huntsman presented to the Evil Queen the heart of which animal?",
    choices: [" Heffalump", " Dragon", " Pig", " Woozle"],
    correctAnswer: 2
}, {
    question: "What did the Prince give to Snow White to awaken her?",
    choices: [" A boop on the nose", " Love's First Kiss", " A sandwich", " True Love's Kiss"],
    correctAnswer: 1
}, {
    question: "The disguised Queen told Snow White that the apple was what kind of apple?",
    choices: [" Caramel", " Space", " Barking", " Wishing"],
    correctAnswer: 3
}, {
    question: "The magically-induced coma from the poisoned apple is called?",
    choices: ["the Sleeping Death", " A Trip to Neverland", " the Choker", " Good Night Snow White"],
    correctAnswer: 0
}, {
    question: "Which of the Dwarfs was reluctant for Snow White to stay?",
    choices: [" Doc", " Monstro", " Stitch", " Grumpy"],
    correctAnswer: 3
}, {
    question: "What do the Dwarfs work in?",
    choices: [" a coffee shop", " a French restaurant", " a mine", " the Haunted Mansion"],
    correctAnswer: 2
}, {
    question: "Who warned Snow White not to let any strangers into the cottage?",
    choices: [" Grumpy", " Dopey", " Sneezy", " Bashful"],
    correctAnswer: 0
}];
